Color
B&W
Gaussian Blur. Kernel size: 11.
Gaussian Blur. Kernel size: 19.
Gaussian Blur. Kernel size: 29.
Bilateral filter(edges are preserved).
Grabbing red object RGB.
Grabbing red object HSV.
Improved grabbing red object HSV.
Horizontal Sobel edge detection. k=1.
Horizontal Sobel edge detection. k=3.
Vertical Sobel edge detection. k=3.
Both edges Sobel. k=3.
Hough circle detection. dp=1.2. min_distance=300. param2=50. minRadius=30. maxRadius=100.
Hough circle detection. dp=1.2. min_distance=400. param2=100. minRadius=100. maxRadius=200.
Hough circle detection. dp=1.2. min_distance=250. param2=150. minRadius=100. maxRadius=180.
Detecting circle in motion.
Likelihood intensity values(Back Projection).
Face and eyes tracking.
Eyes' area color change(party mode).